youngisthan.in 2018-10-27

# Privacy Policy - Youngisthan.in

Last Updated On: 24th October 2013

### Introduction

Welcome to Youngisthan.in (hereinafter “Youngisthan.in”, “Youngisthan”, “Santoshi Media & Entertainments Private Limited”, “we” or “us”). All references to ” “Youngisthan.in”, “Youngisthan”, “Santoshi Media & Entertainments Private Limited”, “we” or “us” in this Privacy Policy shall refer only to Santoshi Media & Entertainments Private Limited.

At Youngisthan.in, privacy is a top priority and we provide this Privacy Policy to outline our practices and procedures with respect to information collection and use to enable you to make an informed decision about sharing information with us.

### Acceptance of Terms

Please read this policy carefully because by visiting this website or domain or other Youngisthan.in Websites or domains (“Website”) and/or sharing information with us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time by us. This page was last updated as of the date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

### Information we Collect

 **Information You Give Us:**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or you provide to us in any other way, such as by telephone or by electronic mail. This information includes your full name, company details, postal address, phone number, email address and your social network profile ID’s.

 **Information Collected Automatically:**  
Youngisthan.in automatically collects certain type of information when you visit our website. This information includes IP address, browser type, referring url, request url, user agent, browser accept language, platform type, date/time stamp and any other data that comes from interaction with Youngisthan.in network.

 **Information Collected by Third Party Tools:**  
Youngisthan.in uses third party services for web analytical puposes. These services are use to collect demographic information, Website surfing patterns, hostnames etc. This information includes IP address, browser type, referring url, request url, user agent, browser accept language, platform type, date/time stamp and any other data that comes from interaction with Youngisthan.in network. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

 **Cookies:**  
We use cookies to keep track of your preferences and settings during the time you view our website. We also use them to recognize return visitors and to track our promotions. We gather this information for internal use only.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history.  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

### Sharing your Information

Youngisthan.in will only share your Information for the limited purposes provided for in this Privacy Policy. This may include sharing Information

  * to comply with applicable laws and regulations
  * to comply with any legal summons, notices, orders, enquiries by law enforcement officials/ quasi-judicial forces.
  * to enforce terms and conditions of the products or services and other agreements.
  * to protect the rights, property, or safety of Youngisthan.in, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * to vendors, administrative service providers, technology providers, and carefully selected partners for data validation, enhancement, information verification and using of third party services or products.
  * for any other purpose for which you provide consent.

The client authorizes Youngisthan.in to exchange, share, part with all information related to the details and transaction history of the clients to its Affiliates / banks / financial institutions / credit bureaus / agencies/ participation in any telecommunication or electronic clearing network as may be required by law, customary practice, credit reporting, statistical analysis and credit scoring, verification or risk management and shall not hold Youngisthan.in liable for use or disclosure of this information.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets. In the event that Youngisthan.in is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

### Electronic Mail

Youngisthan.in may use your personal information to contact you by electronic mail concerning your use of our services. These communications are intended to inform you of important information regarding your account, or about general services or promotional offers provided by Youngisthan.in. If you do not want to receive email from us regarding service updates, please click the “unsubscribe link” at the bottom of any email you receive from Youngisthan.in. We will, however, continue to send you email regarding your account administration and necessary information, such as renewal notices, invoice alerts, administrative emails etc.

### Security

Youngisthan.in employs appropriate measures to ensure the security of all Information, and we routinely evaluate our practices to identify security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our services. No transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when communicating with us.

### Third Party Site Links:

This site contains links to external Web Sites. Youngisthan.in is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Web sites.

### Changes:

As the standards governing Internet privacy continue to evolve, Youngisthan.in may find it appropriate or necessary to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. As a result, we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and shall post such changes on the Website. Our Website will state the date the Privacy Policy was last updated. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you use this Website to make sure you understand how your information will be used.

### Your Representation:

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND APPLICABLE SITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose Information you supply to us with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party’s Information has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party’s Information; (c) which of the third party’s data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about him/her.
